ipaswithchris.com 2011-02-13

# Untitled Document

>   
>  Privacy Policy
> 
> We will notify you of any changes by posting the privacy policy here on this site. Please take the time to review all information below.  
> 
> 
> The personal information we collect includes name and e-mail address and phone number. We use the information that we collect to provide services, fulfill orders, send newsletters and updates in regards to our site. We also use this information directly and indirectly with other parties to introduce other products and services that are either owned by, licensed by, our subsidaries and/or partnering with us. We do this by transfering personal information in hopes of you may be interested in other services and or products offered by other companies similar to Success Copilot Inc. Once a third party obtains your information it's future use is controlled by the business practices of the third party, which is beyond our control. Note however, your payment information is used only for order processing purposes.
> 
> When submitting information on our website you authorize us to use your personal information and consent to receiving email from us as well as periodic phone calls from us in regards to our products and services offered with Success Copilot Inc. You can unsubscribe at anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link found within emails sent from us at any time.
> 
> If you purchase anything through us, we collect credit or debit card information used only for the purposes of completing that transaction. This information includes the neccessary information needed to complete the transaction such as name and card number. We use an unaffiliated credit card merchant to process all orders. The company does not share your information, this information is again used for the sole purpose of processing your transaction.
> 
> Contact us at the address below if you wish to change or delete any information we have about you. We will respond to your request and change any information within (15) business days. 
> 
> DRG Inc, Partnering With Success Copilot Inc  
>  2701 Enterprise Drive Suite #5  
>  Anderson IN, 46013
